some how many people feel obligated to give away their time and energy to arms
一些人感到有义务将自己的时间和精力奉献给武器
with wi-drive feel the need to prove themselves or have that intense desire to
驾驶Wi-Drive的人需要证明自己或有强烈的愿望
be like the problem is that bake noise too much
就像问题是烘烤噪音太多
about a dots of other people you picander servant
约有点点你仆人的人
if you find yourself in this situation wondering his powershare with your power packed with
如果您发现自己处于这种情况下，想知道他的权力与您的权力包装在一起
it to the game you sovereignty and show the
它对游戏的主权，并显示
world that you feel you yourself this method is cold walking ow
你觉得自己的世界，这种方法是行不通的
[Music]
[音乐]
walking with things would get some time seats and necessary measures to the
与事物同行将获得一些时间座位和采取必要的措施
church and soft power over situation in a lifestyle jute variety of people
教会和对黄麻生活方式的控制权
some of these people have difficulties respecting other people's afraid give some
其中有些人在尊重别人的恐惧方面有困难
of them all clean ii and those people greatest songs of you write an der sar
他们中的所有人都很干净，而那些人中你们最伟大的歌曲都写了一个sar
simple cool ass holes that seek to take advantage of people for the red game
简单的酷屁股洞，旨在利用人们的优势进行红色游戏
of you show these people that you willing and able to remove yourself from the
你们向这些人展示了您愿意并且能够将自己从
presents at home at olie send a message that i do not own you that will give you
送礼在家中发送礼物给我，我不拥有你，这会给你
back control over your own faculty the power of working no way as to great
对您自己的教师进行反向控制，无法发挥出色的工作能力
campaigns of the word 0 and 2 direction of you often find yourself wasting your
单词“ 0”和“ 2”的运动常常会浪费自己的精力
time to the wings of other people of caterpillar
时间到了毛毛虫其他人的翅膀
your rafting being sign off and use or just after be used by them at this
您的漂流在此被签收并使用或刚被他们使用
very likely that you have difficulty saying no and of course die traction and
很可能您很难拒绝，当然会失去牵引力，
life the inability to say no and the absence of direction live leads to you
生活无法拒绝，生活缺乏方向会导致您
not vote for review with standing form by easily god
不要投票给容易的上帝以站立形式进行评论
open your fans or other people's fingers wan pipel notice that you
打开粉丝或其他人的手指，请注意
black direction for the sample in the form of commitment your personal goal
承诺您个人目标的形式是样本的黑色方向
they will see your time and less valuable than there this at such a party
他们将在这样的聚会上看到您的时间，并且比那里的价值低
lodge atomizers you doing stuff for them for yourself in their eyes
将雾化器交给您，让他们在自己的眼中为自己做事
you're at least doing something valuable with your time which is being and
你至少正在做一些有价值的事情
utility for their interest however one you are committed to record
为他们的利益效用，但是您承诺要记录
it shows that you value your time and there for your life
它表明您珍惜自己的时间和生命
people will realize that your spending your time
人们会意识到，您花费时间
and be a more important and serving and also by keeping your eyes on the ball
并变得更加重要和发球，并且将视线保持在球上
something a shirt wants and what we want from situations which people fire age of
一件衬衫想要的东西，以及人们在年龄达到某个年龄时所需要的东西
power is of downright buse you this could be the case in
权力是彻头彻尾的忙，你可能就是这种情况
regards to the workplace marriage and the van friendships been
关于工作场所的婚姻和面包车的友谊
tailored to your own pace we even made a yukari less about ifrs or else you could
根据您自己的步调量身定制，我们甚至减少了有关ifrs的yukari，否则您可以
focus on yourself you will not engage media proof of seeking behavior because
专注于自己，您不会参与寻求行为的媒体证明，因为
there's only one person after samples 11 to you walk in your iphone on youtube
样本11之后只有一个人陪伴您在youtube上使用iphone
people and destructive environment will protect yourself respect and integrity
人和破坏性的环境将保护您自己的尊重和正直
it shows the world that you decide en door nat decided for the driver frans
它向世界展示了您决定为司机法兰做出的决定
family and spouse that or do you love them
你爱他们的家庭和配偶
you're not dependent on them and will not stick around 'oh en ik crochet white
您不依赖于它们，也不会黏在身边'哦，en ik钩针编织白色
wreath with shows the person you are doing business with age of plenty of
与一起花圈，显示您正从事经营业务的人
other options despite the fact that you're interested
其他选择，尽管您有兴趣
the deal is not one session for you walking we creates an abundant mindset
这笔交易对您来说不是一个会话，我们会创造出丰富的心态
even if you don't have love of money processions of friendships the signals
即使您不爱金钱，也不会因友谊而游行
that you all other lee content you might like and love certain people in your
您可能喜欢的所有其他Lee内容，并爱您中的某些人
life but you don't need and luxury million dollars in the bank and
生活，但您不需要，可以在银行存入数百万美元，
lamborghini trophy wife is already great what we do the sex journals
兰博基尼奖杯的妻子已经很伟大了，我们在做性杂志
you'll be perfectly fine ass the willingness to balk ow and lien it is
你会很好的屁股愿意拒绝和留置这是
you stronger snow dosage position the guyser way you win
您的雪量越强，您赢得比赛的方式就越多
thank you for what you [Music]
谢谢你的[音乐]
[Music]
[音乐]